Like this…
Environmental injustice I'm
tired and sick of corruption
I don't know who to trust in…
With all this environmental injustice
I'm tired and sick of corruption
I don't know who to trust in
Trying to have my reservations
But I feel like serving the devils
Dessert at his own table cause…
It's an environmental injustice
I'm tired and sick of corruption
Corruption got me real tight
Baby, that's what it feels like
When there's environmental injustice
You're tired and sick of corruption
And you don't know who to trust
People you trusted with your dear life
Somebody knows what it feels like
Environmental injustice I'm
tired and sick of corruption
I don't know who to trust,
I don't know who to trust
They won’t take your home away
If you're covered in blessings
Everyday yeah ,everyday.
Everyday yeah, everyday
Look up to the sky, no room for stressing
Jesus take these thoughts away,
Jesus take these thoughts away
They can't do nothing to you,
they can't do nothing to you
We gon stand here and fight against
what's wrong for what's true
They can't do nothing to you,
they can't do nothing to you
We gon stand here and fight against
what's wrong for what's true
Said we just want it back,
back to the beginning
When everybody cared, like
when everybody winning
Before they blamed the fruit,
before we started sinning
Well this land was mine,
Lord, if only you can dig it
But hold up, let me pivot
They wanna take the church,
probably wanna build a prison
So really what it's giving? Villian
The future got me fighting for the feeling
You see my people moving cause
they able and they willing
To stand up like a building for
these buildings got me building
Pillar of my era and I'm
daring them to kill him
No reason to be scared, be
prepared for the healing
And leave it up to God, oh
yeah, he made me in his image
Corruption got me real tight
Baby that's what it feels like
When there's environmental injustice
You're tired and sick of corruption
And you don't know who to trust
People you trusted with your dear life
Somebody know what it feels like
Environmental injustice
I'm tired and sick of corruption
I don't know who to trust
Cause you looking like prey,
but now I wanna pray for you
See another day for you, yeah yeah
Cause I don't got the time
and I'm really on the chase
Came from GA for you, yeah yeah
Cause you looking like prey,
but now I wanna pray for you
Cause I don't got the time,
I'm really on the chase
In the A, you better be brave
Better be brave
In the A… GA
In the A, in the A
Better be brave, better be brave
In the A, GA
Walk with me down to the A a bit
I'm staying next to the stadium
In the A
GA
Might introduce you to GeorgiaMe
Or a producer, afford the fee
You get the juice from the Georgia peach
In the GA
You better be brave
In the A
GA…
Cause you looking like prey,
but now I wanna pray for you
See another day for you, yeah
Cause I don't got the time
and I'm really on the chase
Came from GA for you, yeah yeah
Cause you looking like prey,
but now I wanna pray for you